The Mysterious Transfer Student
This is Blue Cop.
I have yet to find Heavy Iron's vehicle.
I will resume my patrol.
No sign of any large trailers here either, over.
Ugh...
How can such a big guy be so hard to find?
Maybe he has the power to disappear, like someone else we know.
You two!
Now's not the time to be slacking off!
You startled me!
Alright, alright! Let's get back to the mission! Hup-two, Hup-two! Hurry up!
Alright, we're coming.
Ugh... that naggy little brat.
No complaining!
Everyone, please keep up the search.
Roger that!
Ugh...
They say that sighing chases away good fortune.
Thanks.
That'll be four dollars.
You're charging me for it?!
I was just kidding. Here.
I know how you must be feeling.
We can't find Heavy Iron, who defeated Blue Cop.
And we don't know who the Metal Cardbot who helped us out was.
So, are you telling me to be patient,
and that they'll all turn up in due time?
No, I think we'd better hurry.
Looks like it's going to rain.
Oh no! I gotta get going then!
When everyone gets back, tell them to get inside the garage.
Alright. Take care!
Later!
Is all this rain also because I sighed?
Hey you!
Watch where you're driving, will ya?!
Alright class, settle down! We have a new student joining us today!
Come on in.
Please introduce yourself.
My name is Crest.
Nice to meet you all.
Ah!
Ah! He's so handsome!
He'll make my channel blow up!
What are they all squealing about, huh?!
He's not so handsome. Am I right, Jun?
To real men, looks aren't important! It's what's on the inside that counts!
Right, Anna?
Ah... good looks really are everything!
That's enough, everyone! Now let's see...
You can go sit behind Vance over there.
Thank you very much, teacher.
That's a nice watch you're wearing.
y-yeah...
Let's get started with the lesson, then. Please open your textbooks to page 48.
Crest, where did you move here from?
Eastpolis.
I had to move here because of my parents' jobs.
I'm not familiar with this town yet. Do you think you could show me around sometime?
-Of course!
-Any time!
Thank you, I appreciate it.
Hmph! Just look at that jerk. He's already making moves!
Let's see how he likes this!
Watch out!
Huh?!
You should be more careful, Vance.
How do you know my name?!
I already know everyone's names. I memorized the list of students enrolled here.
C'mon, that's a lie!
I'm not lying, Lavi.
That's Theo behind you.
And Anna...
Vera...
Kate...
Helena...
And Naomi.
Wow, that's amazing!
Just give me back the ball!
Take it from me, then.
It's mine now!
Stop moving!
It went in!
Such a good shot!
Just a little trick I learned.
Hey Vance, wait up!
Did I overdo it?
Not even Vance could do a thing...
So his name is Crest?
You find the new kid suspicious?
There's something about the way he looks and acts...
It just doesn't seem right.
Hehe! Are you sure you're not just jealous that Anna is into him?
Argh, it's not that! He took an interest in my Metal Breath too!
Something does seem a little off...
What are you two talking about?
Aaah!
C-Crest, what are you doing here?
I'm sorry, I hope now's not a bad time?
Anna, did you bring him here?
Well, of course!
Crest said he has something he wants to talk to you about.
You should have said something before coming!
Why? You'd just be riding around on your bike anyway.
This isn't a playground for kids. You should all head home already.
But Jun can stay?!
I never gave him permission either. He just barges in whenever he wants!
Wah? Now you're just being mean, Uncle Edo! You told me I could come hang out any time-
T-That's for sale! You shouldn't touch it!
I'm sorry, I haven't seen a car like this before-
Haha, no way, are you serious?! There are so many of these c-cars around here!
Y-yeah...
You only moved here recently, so that's probably why it's new to you...
It looks a lot like the R48 used in highway patrol,
but the shape of the hood and exhaust pipes are different.
Woah, Crest! You're an expert on cars too?!
Well, this is a custom vehicle. It's been modified according to the owner's specifications.
Hmm... Is that so?
Haha, y-yeah! That's why!
But what did you want to talk about?
Sorry for the sudden request, but I have a favor to ask.
Just say the word! Crest can ask for anything he wants!
That's not for you to decide!
Aah! Guys!
What's wrong, Anna?!
W-what is it?!
That's...
That's the Metal Cardbot from the other day!
The views will be out of this world!
Bring me Blue Cop. I know he's hiding here somewhere!
W-what? Lemme see who we're dealing with!
Hang on. We'll be discovered if we make a move now.
Come out and show yourself, you coward!
I'm back. I didn't find any leads either.
Isn't that...!
What's going on, who is this guy?
H-Hello, first responders! Over here!
Ah! O-oh, right!
Come on, let's go!
But I'm not even hurt!
Uh... just get in for now!
Jun? Aren't you coming?!
W-well.. uhh... there's no space for me in there!
I have my bike, so I'll go by myself, o-okay?
Theo, take care of them, okay?
Okay. You be careful too.
The coast is clear, Blue Cop!
You, identify yourself.
My name is Wild Guardy. And I am going to be king of the Metal Cardbots!
Ha! King of us? What a joke.
Hang on! Wild Guardy. Weren't you on our side?
Yeah! You helped us in the battle against Heavy Iron, remember?
Hmph. Do not be mistaken. I just didn't want a bunch of weaklings to steal my victory.
What?
The one who will take you down shall be I;
The great, Wild Guardy!
Jun!
Metal Breath, pickup!
Blue Cop, setup!
Blue Cop! Burst Shot!
Burst Shot!
Way to go!
Yeah well, that thing's got nothing on my shield!
I hope that's not all you've got?
Of course not!
Blue Cop! Thunderbolt Smash!
Thunderbolt...
Smash!!
Thunderbolt Smash didn't work.
My shield has been tempered by the magma of planet Machina for over thousands of years.
Your feeble attacks are useless!
Wild... Slash!
Blue Cop!
Hey! You alright?
Jun! Tag me in!
It's no use.
You're no match for me.
Huh? What did you say?
Haaaaaaaa haa!
///
Are you okay, Blue bro?
Since when did you and Blue Cop become brothers?
Another pest has shown up.
I'll be waiting for our next showdown, Blue Cop.
Come back, Wild Guardy...!
Blue Cop!
B-Blue Cop, are you alright?!
Say something, Blue Cop!